<edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry-array>
  <edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
    <title>RIP, sf writer John M Ford</title>
    <author>Cory Doctorow</author>
    <body>Stefan Jones sez, &quot;Science fiction writer and game designer John M. Ford passed away last night. I&apos;ll leave the dignified tributes to others, and present a sample of how I best knew the guy, namely his hilarious off-the-cuff riffs posted on Making Light. One of the posters in the commemoration thread found this recipe for Hot Gingered Pygmy Mammoth:&quot; Preheat a giant turtle shell over a fumarole. A big giant turtle. Put some oil in there. Make sure no other giant turtles are around to see you do this.
On a flat rock, stirring with your Stick of the Dining God, dry cook the sesame seeds over medium heat until they are brown and smell good. Remove from the heat. Add the noodles to the turtle shell and fry fast until puffy and the color of sunrise. Remove from the oil and drain on non-itchy leaves. Throw salt. Set aside.
Sear the mammoth meat on the flat rock. Salt but don’t overdo it, you remember what happened to the Chest-Clutching Tribe of the Plains. Drain. Link (Thanks, Stefan!)
</body>
    <image>http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?i=4ka8a4</image>
    <date>2006-09-25 15:49:58.0 PDT</date>
    <link>http://www.boingboing.net/2006/09/25/rip_sf_writer_john_m.html</link>
    <html>&lt;strong&gt;Cory Doctorow&lt;/strong&gt;:
Stefan Jones sez, &quot;Science fiction writer and game designer John M. Ford passed away last night. I&apos;ll leave the dignified tributes to others, and present a sample of how I best knew the guy, namely his hilarious off-the-cuff riffs posted on &lt;I&gt;Making Light&lt;/I&gt;. One of the posters in the &lt;A href=&quot;http://nielsenhayden.com/makinglight/archives/008033.html#008033&quot;&gt;commemoration thread&lt;/A&gt; found this recipe for Hot Gingered Pygmy Mammoth:&quot;

&lt;blockquote&gt;Preheat a giant turtle shell over a fumarole. A big giant turtle. Put some oil in there. Make sure no other giant turtles are around to see you do this.
&lt;p&gt;
On a flat rock, stirring with your Stick of the Dining God, dry cook the sesame seeds over medium heat until they are brown and smell good. Remove from the heat. Add the noodles to the turtle shell and fry fast until puffy and the color of sunrise. Remove from the oil and drain on non-itchy leaves. Throw salt. Set aside.
&lt;p&gt;
Sear the mammoth meat on the flat rock. Salt but don’t overdo it, you remember what happened to the Chest-Clutching Tribe of the Plains. Drain.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;http://nielsenhayden.com/makinglight/archives/006945.html#100583&quot;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;

(&lt;i&gt;Thanks, &lt;a href=&quot;http://home.comcast.net/%7Estefan_jones/kira_grinning_lo.JPG&quot;&gt;Stefan&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/i&gt;)
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?a=4ka8a4&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?i=4ka8a4&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</html>
  </edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
  <edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
    <title>BillMonk: Roommate-ware for splitting bills</title>
    <author>Cory Doctorow</author>
    <body>H1kari sez, &quot;When I shared an apartment, there was constant tension over who owed for utilities and beer. Later in life, my girlfriend and I would often argue over who paid last time. Now, a site called BillMonk lets you enter shared bills and objectively know where you stand with your friends. When you&apos;re on the go, you can record debts from your phone via SMS. The notion of borrowing is extended to include your personal library so you can track which things are lent out. There&apos;s all sorts of cool features like auto-splitting bills, ties into amazon&apos;s product lookup system for tracking your book collection, etc. I&apos;ve found it super useful, so just thought I&apos;d share it!&quot; Link (Thanks, H1kar1!) 
</body>
    <image>http://craphound.com/images/billmonkmasthead.jpg</image>
    <date>2006-09-25 15:48:12.0 PDT</date>
    <link>http://www.boingboing.net/2006/09/25/billmonk_roommatewar.html</link>
    <html>&lt;strong&gt;Cory Doctorow&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;img src=&quot;http://craphound.com/images/billmonkmasthead.jpg&quot; width=&quot;139&quot; height=&quot;66&quot; align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;

H1kari sez, &quot;When I shared an apartment, there was constant tension over who owed for utilities and beer. Later in life, my girlfriend and I would often argue over who paid last time. Now, a site called BillMonk lets you enter shared bills and objectively know where you stand with your friends. When you&apos;re on the go, you can record debts from your phone via SMS. The notion of borrowing is extended to include your personal library so you can track which things are lent out. There&apos;s all sorts of cool features like auto-splitting bills, ties into amazon&apos;s product lookup system for tracking your book collection, etc. I&apos;ve found it super useful, so just thought I&apos;d share it!&quot;

&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.billmonk.com&quot;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;

(&lt;i&gt;Thanks, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.toorcon.org&quot;&gt;H1kar1&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/i&gt;)

&lt;br clear=&quot;all&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?a=WPXOCU&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?i=WPXOCU&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</html>
  </edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
  <edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
    <title>Drew Friedman&apos;s Old Jewish Comedians</title>
    <author>David Pescovitz</author>
    <body>Drew Friedman is my absolute favorite caricaturist and probably my favorite living portrait artist. His insane attention to detail and mastery of stippling gives his portraits a surreal-yet-oddly lifelike quality. Mark F. and I can&apos;t stop talking about his latest book, Old Jewish Comedians, published by Fantagraphics as part of their excellent BLAB! Storybook series. (Link to Mark&apos;s review at Mad Professor.) Friedman takes on all the greats, from Jack Benny, Don Rickles, and the Marx Brothers to Henny Youngman, Bud Abbott, and Sid Caesar. The portraits not only exude the charisma of these funny men but somehow manage to feel &quot;of the time&quot; too. And as Mark said, Friedman is a master at drawing liver spots. Highly recommended. Link 
</body>
    <image>http://www.boingboing.net/images/_Resources_Jewish-Comedians.jpg</image>
    <date>2006-09-25 15:38:23.0 PDT</date>
    <link>http://www.boingboing.net/2006/09/25/drew_friedmans_old_j.html</link>
    <html>&lt;strong&gt;David Pescovitz&lt;/strong&gt;:

&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.boingboing.net/images/_Resources_Jewish-Comedians.jpg&quot; height=&quot;250&quot; width=&quot;239&quot; border=&quot;1&quot; align=&quot;left&quot; hspace=&quot;4&quot; vspace=&quot;4&quot; alt=&quot; Resources Jewish-Comedians&quot; /&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.drewfriedmanart.com/&quot;&gt;Drew Friedman&lt;/a&gt; is my absolute favorite caricaturist and probably my favorite living portrait artist. His insane attention to detail and mastery of stippling gives his portraits a surreal-yet-oddly lifelike quality. Mark F. and I can&apos;t stop talking about his latest book, Old Jewish Comedians, published by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fantagraphics.com&quot;&gt;Fantagraphics&lt;/a&gt; as part of their excellent BLAB! Storybook series. (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.madprofessor.net/2006/09/old_jewish_comedians.html&quot;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt; to Mark&apos;s review at Mad Professor.) Friedman takes on all the greats, from Jack Benny, Don Rickles, and the Marx Brothers to Henny Youngman, Bud Abbott, and Sid Caesar. The portraits not only exude the charisma of these funny men but somehow manage to feel &quot;of the time&quot; too. And as Mark said, Friedman is a master at drawing liver spots. Highly recommended. &lt;br clear=&quot;all&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1560977418/boingboing0e-20/&quot;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?a=nYveMM&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?i=nYveMM&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</html>
  </edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
  <edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
    <title>HOWTO poach salmon in your dishwasher</title>
    <author>David Pescovitz</author>
    <body>It reminds me a little of Seinfeld&apos;s Kramer prepping food in his shower, but Wine X Magazine has a recipe for poaching salmon in your dishwasher. This odd HOWTO was written by Bob Blumer, author of the book Surreal Gourmet. From the recipe: DO NOT ATTEMPT TO COOK A WHOLE FISH!
1 Place fish packets on the top rack.
2 Add dirty dishes and lemon-scented soap. This optional step is not recommended for novices. However, as long as the salmon&apos;s tightly sealed in its aluminum foil packet, it won&apos;t absorb any soapy taste or smell.
3 Set dishwasher to the &quot;normal&quot; cycle. Modern dishwashers have &quot;economy&quot; and &quot;cool dry&quot; settings, which are undesirable since they conserve heat. However, on the other end of the spectrum, the &quot;pots and pans&quot; setting tends to overcook the fish.
4 Run salmon through the entire wash-and-dry cycle -- approximately 50 minutes for most models.
5 When cycle&apos;s complete, take salmon out, discard foil, place one fillet on each plate and spoon a generous serving of dill sauce on top. Link 
</body>
    <image>http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?i=riQ7kY</image>
    <date>2006-09-25 15:18:22.0 PDT</date>
    <link>http://www.boingboing.net/2006/09/25/howto_poach_salmon_i.html</link>
    <html>&lt;strong&gt;David Pescovitz&lt;/strong&gt;:
It reminds me a little of Seinfeld&apos;s Kramer prepping food in his shower, but Wine X Magazine has a recipe for poaching salmon in your dishwasher. This odd HOWTO was written by Bob Blumer, author of the book &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0811801217/boingboing0e-20/&quot;&gt;Surreal Gourmet&lt;/a&gt;. From the recipe:
&lt;blockquote&gt;DO NOT ATTEMPT TO COOK A WHOLE FISH!
&lt;br&gt;&lt;Br&gt;
1 Place fish packets on the top rack.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;Br&gt;
2 Add dirty dishes and lemon-scented soap. This optional step is not recommended for novices. However, as long as the salmon&apos;s tightly sealed in its aluminum foil packet, it won&apos;t absorb any soapy taste or smell.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;Br&gt;
3 Set dishwasher to the &quot;normal&quot; cycle. Modern dishwashers have &quot;economy&quot; and &quot;cool dry&quot; settings, which are undesirable since they conserve heat. However, on the other end of the spectrum, the &quot;pots and pans&quot; setting tends to overcook the fish.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;Br&gt;
4 Run salmon through the entire wash-and-dry cycle -- approximately 50 minutes for most models.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;Br&gt;
5 When cycle&apos;s complete, take salmon out, discard foil, place one fillet on each plate and spoon a generous serving of dill sauce on top. &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.winexmagazine.com/index.php/wine/vieweat/dishwasher-salmon/&quot;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?a=riQ7kY&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?i=riQ7kY&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</html>
  </edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
  <edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
    <title>Marmaduke comics explained</title>
    <author>Mark Frauenfelder</author>
    <body>Each day, Joe Mathlete posts the Marmaduke comic on his blog, along with an explanation. It&apos;s terrific. Marmaduke spots a smaller dog being toted around the block while on his afternoon walk, envies its portability and general lifestyle, decides he is sick of walking, and demands that Owner-Lady suck it up and carry him. Owner-Lady balks. Marmaduke ordered a pizza from 2 Ur Door Pizza! and tipped one of the delivery persons (2 Ur Door Pizza pizzas take two people to deliver them) a bone. As Marmaduke is a dog, and dogs consider bones to be very important and valuable, he no doubt was being earnest and generous in his offer, but the delivery boy has not encountered such before.
(A lesser strip would have pointed out the absurdity in a dog ordering pizza (&quot;how can such a thing be?!?&quot;), but the humor in Marmaduke is much more subtle and layered to settle for such an obvious chuckle. In the Marmadukiverse (c), this sort of shit happens all the time.) Link (Thanks, Sergio!) 
</body>
    <image>http://www.boingboing.net/200609251158.jpg</image>
    <date>2006-09-25 13:09:46.0 PDT</date>
    <link>http://www.boingboing.net/2006/09/25/marmaduke_comics_exp.html</link>
    <html>&lt;strong&gt;Mark Frauenfelder&lt;/strong&gt;:
Each day, Joe Mathlete posts the Marmaduke comic on his blog, along with an explanation. It&apos;s terrific.


&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.boingboing.net/200609251158.jpg&quot; height=&quot;169&quot; width=&quot;170&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; align=&quot;left&quot; hspace=&quot;4&quot; vspace=&quot;4&quot; alt=&quot;200609251158&quot; /&gt; 
Marmaduke spots a smaller dog being toted around the block while on his afternoon walk, envies its portability and general lifestyle, decides he is sick of walking, and demands that Owner-Lady suck it up and carry him. Owner-Lady balks.&lt;br clear=&quot;all&quot;&gt;


&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.boingboing.net/200609251200.jpg&quot; height=&quot;169&quot; width=&quot;168&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; align=&quot;left&quot; hspace=&quot;4&quot; vspace=&quot;4&quot; alt=&quot;200609251200&quot; /&gt; 
Marmaduke ordered a pizza from 2 Ur Door Pizza! and tipped one of the delivery persons (2 Ur Door Pizza pizzas take two people to deliver them) a bone. As Marmaduke is a dog, and dogs consider bones to be very important and valuable, he no doubt was being earnest and generous in his offer, but the delivery boy has not encountered such before.

&lt;P&gt;(A lesser strip would have pointed out the absurdity in a dog ordering pizza (&quot;how can such a thing be?!?&quot;), but the humor in Marmaduke is much more subtle and layered to settle for such an obvious chuckle. In the Marmadukiverse (c), this sort of shit happens all the time.)&lt;/blockquote&gt;



 &lt;a href=&quot;http://marmadukeexplained.blogspot.com/&quot;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Thanks, &lt;a href=&quot;Sergio&quot;&gt;Sergio&lt;/a&gt;!)&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?a=FfL3xv&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?i=FfL3xv&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</html>
  </edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
  <edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
    <title>Article on classic toy designer John McNett</title>
    <author>Mark Frauenfelder</author>
    <body>Scott and Brian say: Today the Mego Museum is featuring a great article on John and Linda McNett, a couple who met while working as toy designers at Mego Corp in the mid 1970&apos;s.  In addition to working on many great Mego products such as 2XL -- One of the first interactive electronic toys, the Micronauts, and World&apos;s Greatest Super Heroes, John worked on Etch-a-Sketch, Magna Doodle, and designed the look of the Colecovision system and Coleco&apos;s minitabletop arcade games like Pac Man and Frogger. It&apos;s a cool insight into the orgins of our favorite toys written by Ben Holcomb, author of the forthcoming book World&apos;s Greatest Toys. Link 
</body>
    <image>http://www.boingboing.net/200609251017.jpg</image>
    <date>2006-09-25 11:17:59.0 PDT</date>
    <link>http://www.boingboing.net/2006/09/25/article_on_classic_t.html</link>
    <html>&lt;strong&gt;Mark Frauenfelder&lt;/strong&gt;:
Scott and Brian say:

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.boingboing.net/200609251017.jpg&quot; height=&quot;169&quot; width=&quot;233&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; align=&quot;left&quot; hspace=&quot;4&quot; vspace=&quot;4&quot; alt=&quot;200609251017&quot; /&gt;
Today the Mego Museum is featuring a great article on John and Linda McNett, a couple who met while working as toy designers at Mego Corp in the mid 1970&apos;s.  In addition to working on many great Mego products such as 2XL -- One of the first interactive electronic toys, the Micronauts, and World&apos;s Greatest Super Heroes, John worked on Etch-a-Sketch, Magna Doodle, and designed the look of the Colecovision system and Coleco&apos;s minitabletop arcade games like Pac Man and Frogger. It&apos;s a cool insight into the orgins of our favorite toys written by Ben Holcomb, author of the forthcoming book World&apos;s Greatest Toys.&lt;br clear=&quot;all&quot;&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.megomuseum.com/megolibrary/interviews/mcnett/mcnett.html&quot;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?a=tO4R8c&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?i=tO4R8c&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</html>
  </edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
  <edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
    <title>Radar interview with John Hodgman</title>
    <author>Mark Frauenfelder</author>
    <body>Radar interviews the wonderful John Hodgman. Radar: And then there&apos;s The Daily Show. Talk about a sweet gig.
JH: It is so incredibly unexpected and providential as to be frightening to even discuss with you now.
Radar: Is Jon Stewart as Waspy in person as he appears on television?
JH: I&apos;m not going to get into ethnic phrenology with you. He&apos;s a very handsome man who is of average height.
Radar: With all of this appearing in front of the camera, one could conclude you harbor a desire to act. Do you?
JH: I am not an actor, but I am not averse to the idea of being a personality. For me the best example is George Plimpton, who chased after every adventure with very little prejudice, always with an open mind and often with a funny accent. I am on top of a roller coaster that I never expected to be on. I don&apos;t know what&apos;s going to happen when the roller coaster goes down. My guess is I will fly out and I will hit a pole. Link 
</body>
    <image>http://www.boingboing.net/200609251002.jpg</image>
    <date>2006-09-25 11:03:46.0 PDT</date>
    <link>http://www.boingboing.net/2006/09/25/radar_interview_with.html</link>
    <html>&lt;strong&gt;Mark Frauenfelder&lt;/strong&gt;:
Radar interviews the wonderful John Hodgman.

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.boingboing.net/200609251002.jpg&quot; height=&quot;169&quot; width=&quot;126&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; align=&quot;left&quot; hspace=&quot;4&quot; vspace=&quot;4&quot; alt=&quot;200609251002&quot; /&gt;
Radar: And then there&apos;s &lt;em&gt;The Daily Show&lt;/em&gt;. Talk about a sweet gig.
&lt;BR&gt;JH: It is so incredibly unexpected and providential as to be frightening to even discuss with you now.

&lt;P&gt;Radar: Is Jon Stewart as Waspy in person as he appears on television?
&lt;BR&gt;JH: I&apos;m not going to get into ethnic phrenology with you. He&apos;s a very handsome man who is of average height.

&lt;P&gt;Radar: With all of this appearing in front of the camera, one could conclude you harbor a desire to act. Do you?
&lt;BR&gt;JH: I am not an actor, but I am not averse to the idea of being a personality. For me the best example is George Plimpton, who chased after every adventure with very little prejudice, always with an open mind and often with a funny accent. I am on top of a roller coaster that I never expected to be on. I don&apos;t know what&apos;s going to happen when the roller coaster goes down. My guess is I will fly out and I will hit a pole. &lt;br clear=&quot;all&quot;&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.radaronline.com/features/2006/09/hodgmania.php&quot;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?a=VmfsQA&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?i=VmfsQA&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</html>
  </edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
  <edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
    <title>Project to make Marmaduke less unfunny</title>
    <author>Mark Frauenfelder</author>
    <body>Of the three least funny dog comic strips on the planet (Fred Basset, Howard Huge, and Marmaduke), Marmaduke is the unfunniest. The folks at the Marmaduke Project are attempting to make Marmaduke not suck so much by modifying his cartoons in a variety of ways. Link (Thanks, Erin!) 
</body>
    <image>http://www.boingboing.net/marmaduke200609250957.jpg</image>
    <date>2006-09-25 10:57:58.0 PDT</date>
    <link>http://www.boingboing.net/2006/09/25/project_to_make_marm.html</link>
    <html>&lt;strong&gt;Mark Frauenfelder&lt;/strong&gt;:

&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.boingboing.net/marmaduke200609250957.jpg&quot; height=&quot;358&quot; width=&quot;299&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; align=&quot;left&quot; hspace=&quot;4&quot; vspace=&quot;4&quot; alt=&quot;200609250957&quot; /&gt;
Of the three least funny dog comic strips on the planet (Fred Basset, Howard Huge, and Marmaduke), Marmaduke is the unfunniest. The folks at the Marmaduke Project are attempting to make Marmaduke not suck so much by modifying his cartoons in a variety of ways. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.supermasterpiece.com/marmaduke/&quot;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Thanks, Erin!)&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?a=NU6keZ&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?i=NU6keZ&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</html>
  </edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
  <edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
    <title>Guy uses VR goggles to pilot RC plane</title>
    <author>Mark Frauenfelder</author>
    <body>Video of a guy who put a wireless camera on a model plane and wears VR goggles to pilot it. Link 
</body>
    <image>http://www.boingboing.net/vrplanePicture%202-16.jpg</image>
    <date>2006-09-25 10:46:52.0 PDT</date>
    <link>http://www.boingboing.net/2006/09/25/guy_uses_vr_goggles_.html</link>
    <html>&lt;strong&gt;Mark Frauenfelder&lt;/strong&gt;:

&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.boingboing.net/vrplanePicture%202-16.jpg&quot; height=&quot;74&quot; width=&quot;100&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; align=&quot;left&quot; hspace=&quot;4&quot; vspace=&quot;4&quot; alt=&quot;Picture 2-16&quot; /&gt;



&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.boingboing.net/vrplanePicture%204-10.jpg&quot; height=&quot;76&quot; width=&quot;100&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; align=&quot;left&quot; hspace=&quot;4&quot; vspace=&quot;4&quot; alt=&quot;Picture 4-10&quot; /&gt;



&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.boingboing.net/VRplanePicture%205-12.jpg&quot; height=&quot;77&quot; width=&quot;100&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; align=&quot;left&quot; hspace=&quot;4&quot; vspace=&quot;4&quot; alt=&quot;Picture 5-12&quot; /&gt;

Video of a guy who put a wireless camera on a model plane and wears VR goggles to pilot it. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.therawfeed.com/2006/09/vr-gear-makes-rc-airplane-coolest-toy.html&quot;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?a=5s9Ab4&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?i=5s9Ab4&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</html>
  </edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
  <edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
    <title>Wired News on future body hackers</title>
    <author>David Pescovitz</author>
    <body>Chris Oakes wrote an interesting feature for Wired News about state-of-the-art bionics and individuals who are itching to upgrade their own bodies whether they &quot;need&quot; it or not. The article, titled &quot;What if Bionics Were Better&quot; is the final part in Wired News&apos;s excellent series on artificial limbs and neuroprosthetics. From Oakes&apos;s article: Phillipa Garner is a self-described &quot;gender-hacker.&quot;

In 1993 at the age of 51, she underwent sex reassignment surgery. That was just the beginning of her quest for self-improvement. She followed the sex change with more modification: vaginoplasty, brow reduction, cheek implants, breast implants, lip augmentation and a face-lift. And she&apos;d happily sign up for more, she says.

&quot;I would be inclined to go through with some pretty radical conceptual self-improvement procedures,&quot; Garner said. &quot;I think of cosmetic surgery as collaborative art.... And when I next have disposable income, I&apos;ll be back in the O.R...&quot;

To Garner, surgical enhancements fall right in line with her vocation. A freelance illustrator whose work includes monthly satire in Car &amp; Driver magazine based on cheekily modified car concepts, she has also produced a stream of personal vehicle designs for more efficient transport of the human body.

Whether she&apos;s modifiying vehicles or her own body, it&apos;s all part of the same quest for improvement.

&quot;I felt that my situation in general was screaming out for a monkey wrench in the works,&quot; she said.  Link 
</body>
    <image>http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?i=3YCW1r</image>
    <date>2006-09-25 10:44:31.0 PDT</date>
    <link>http://www.boingboing.net/2006/09/25/wired_news_on_future.html</link>
    <html>&lt;strong&gt;David Pescovitz&lt;/strong&gt;:
Chris Oakes wrote an interesting feature for Wired News about state-of-the-art bionics and individuals who are itching to upgrade their own bodies whether they &quot;need&quot; it or not. The article, titled &quot;What if Bionics Were Better&quot; is the final part in Wired News&apos;s excellent series on artificial limbs and neuroprosthetics. From Oakes&apos;s article:
&lt;blockquote&gt;Phillipa Garner is a self-described &quot;gender-hacker.&quot;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
In 1993 at the age of 51, she underwent sex reassignment surgery. That was just the beginning of her quest for self-improvement. She followed the sex change with more modification: vaginoplasty, brow reduction, cheek implants, breast implants, lip augmentation and a face-lift. And she&apos;d happily sign up for more, she says.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&quot;I would be inclined to go through with some pretty radical conceptual self-improvement procedures,&quot; Garner said. &quot;I think of cosmetic surgery as collaborative art.... And when I next have disposable income, I&apos;ll be back in the O.R...&quot;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
To Garner, surgical enhancements fall right in line with her vocation. A freelance illustrator whose work includes monthly satire in Car &amp; Driver magazine based on cheekily modified car concepts, she has also produced a stream of personal vehicle designs for more efficient transport of the human body.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Whether she&apos;s modifiying vehicles or her own body, it&apos;s all part of the same quest for improvement.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&quot;I felt that my situation in general was screaming out for a monkey wrench in the works,&quot; she said.  &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://wired.com/news/technology/0,71840-0.html?tw=wn_index_1&quot;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?a=3YCW1r&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://feeds.feedburner.com/~a/boingboing/iBag?i=3YCW1r&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</html>
  </edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry>
</edu.stanford.hci.r3.demos.blog.BoingBoingEntry-array>